hey there this is a correction to next
episode you are seeing a sneak peek of
state of project by episode 16 but the
correction is relevant to what is going
to be in the next episode
so listen carefully
if your grid is not square shape
so this end length is not equal
then when you will be past finding it
will be throwing an error like this
i made a crucial mistake inside the init
method in the past finding
i accidentally flipped the width and
length
so to fix this error
your init should look like this
in the next episode check the pin
comment for code if you will need a
reminder how it should look like when i
will be talking about init
you